Roman Svyatnenko - Android developer

Information

Personal:

• E-mail: romeo97934@gmail.com

Phone: +38093-053-52-04
Date of birth: 30.06.1997
Citizenship: Ukraine
Maritalstatus: single

Social:

• GitHub: https://github.com/PIBODIBU

• Skype: live:cup.cake_10

Web site: http://nauguide.esy.es/#/projectsTwitter: https://twitter.com/doge_nakamoto

Languages:

• English - fluent

• Ukrainian - native

• Russian - native

Summary

I'm an Android developer with 3 years of experience. My strong personal qualities: responsibility, full commitment to work, perseverance, calmness, openness. My main goal is to develop myself as an Android developer, so I give myself completely to my work. I see myself as part of a large team that develops interesting products in the field of information technology.

Portfolio

http://nauguide.esy.es/#/projects

Main skills

Java SE

Rank 9/10

Frameworks & Libraries

- JavaFX
- Swing

Android

Rank 9/10

Frameworks & Libraries

- Butterknife
- Retrofit
- Picasso
- Glide

- Data Binding
- Realm
- Android Support Libraries
- Android Design Libraries
- Android Support Annotations

Java EE

Rank 8/10

Frameworks & Libraries

- Spring
- Hibernate
- JPA
- Thymeleaf

HTML

Rank 9/10

Frameworks & Libraries

• Angluar Material

CSS

Rank 8/10

Javascript

Rank 7/10

Frameworks & Libraries

• AngularJS

Additional skills

- UI/UX Creating user-friendly interfaces
- Programming patterns MVC, MVP, MVVP
- Client-server programming Client-server interaction via REST API
- Maven, Gradle Project management & Build tools
- Git Version control systems
- Trello Development tracking
- REST

Experience

Android developer in Studio Vision

01 August 2016 – 01 September 2016

Freelancer as Android developer

January 2015 - Now

Education

National Aviation University, Institute of Computer Information Technologies - Higher education, Bachelor

01 September 2014 – 01 June 2018

Additional

English courses Speaking Fish 30 September 2015 – 30 June 2016